[
  {
    "id": "5b48e785f188271082d48c55,",
    "question": "019",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "id": "5b4901f0a471374981213325,",
    "question": "019",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": "5b4901f0a471374981213326,",
    "question": "019",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e99cf5654512251ecf3a,",
    "question": "022",
    "answer": "true"
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e99cf5654512251ecf39",
    "question": "028",
    "answer": "Nope, the way is free"
  },
  {
    "id": "5b49033bc07c73146d1a1804",
    "question": "028",
    "answer": null
  },
  {
    "id": "5b49033bc07c7313891a1806",
    "question": "028",
    "answer": "Don't know. I didn't check, it's my luch time now."
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e785f188271082d48c55",
    "question": "028",
    "answer": "There is a fu*ki*g apple tree in the way !"
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e785f188271082d48c54",
    "question": "042",
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e912a47c7411ed895842",
    "question": "042",
    "answer": "41"
  },
  {
    "id": "5b48e912a47c7411ed895843,",
    "question": "042",
    "answer": "44"
  }
]
